#### Contact

pkasture2010@gmail.com

www.linkedin.com/in/priyankakasture (LinkedIn)

## Top Skills

Entrepreneurship
Social Media Marketing
Community Management

### Languages

Spanish (Elementary)
English (Full Professional)
Hindi (Limited Working)

#### Certifications

Deep Learning and Computer Vision
Python Masterclass
Algorithms - Design and Analysis
Statistical Learning

# Priyanka Kasture

Founder - Machine Learning India Pune

## Summary

Entrepreneurial, data-driven social media marketing strategist with an excellent understanding of creation, management and monetization of large online consumer-communities.

I am also the founder of Machine Learning India, India's leading social media driven machine learning community with over 300,000 members.

I am obsessed with customers, with quality, and I love to apply consumer-psychology methods and practices to marketing and branding.

I specialize in: Content marketing, social media analytics, online brand strategy, business story-telling, consumer-psychology, online community management, influencer and affiliate marketing.

Speaking Enagagments: PICT, Vishwakarma IoIT, Sinhgad COE and Cummins COE, TomTom India, Securly Software, Globant India and GS Labs.

Get in touch with me on: pkasture2010@gmail.com.

## Experience

Machine Learning India 2 years 6 months

Content Strategist
April 2018 - Present (2 years 5 months)
Pune, Maharashtra

 Single handedly created and successfully monetizing Machine Learning India, India's biggest, social-media driven, AI and ML community, with over 300,000 members.

- Hacked the growth of the online-community, resulting in the addition of 25,000 30,000 new members to the community, every month.
- Generating content marketing strategies that are resulting in a cumulative reach of 5,50,000 to 6,00,000, distinct people per week.
- Creating appealing design assets to construct a strong brand-image in the minds of the members of the community.
- Collaborating with various content creators, researchers and influential personalities in the AI/ML niche to boost the growth of the community on all platforms.

#### Founder

March 2018 - Present (2 years 6 months)

Pune, Maharashtra, India

Machine Learning India (MLI), is a thriving community of 300,000 ardent - artificial intelligence enthusiasts across India and the globe. The goal of MLI is to reduce the skill-gap in India, by creating a vibrant AI ecosystem and talent pool; thereby leading our country to have a significant take in the global AI revolution. To pursue the same, MLI intends to democratize quality technical education and make it available to all.

MLI is present on Instagram, Telegram, Linkedin, Twitter and YouTube.

The Apprentice Project - TAP Course Facilitator August 2018 - February 2020 (1 year 7 months) Pune Area, India

Served as a Visual-Arts facilitator at iTeachSVT School, Hadapsar, under The Apprentice Project, which is a Teach For India fellow led initiative, that connects skilled, motivated individuals to underprivileged children through an immersive mentorship program.

## TechGig Influencer August 2018 - November 2018 (4 months) India

Served as a social media influencer for TechGig's Geek Goddess Campaign by deploying digital marketing methodologies, to increase campaign awareness.

Surge, One Bit Technology Technology Evangelist September 2018 - October 2018 (2 months)

Pune Area, India

Served as an AI Evangelist and Community Manager at Surge AI Labs (SAIL).

## Education

University of Pune

Bachelor's Degree, Information Technology · (2015 - 2019)

Modern Education Society's Nowrosjee Wadia College Arts, Science, Pune 01

Junior College, Electronics · (2013 - 2015)